# ux designer

07722 195 565 me@danguydesign.com danguydesign.com

# **About Me**

I am a UX Designer with over **3.5 years of experience in web design**. I have a proven track record in improving usability and increasing Conversion Rate. I am confident in leading workshops and delivering presentations to gain stakeholder buy-in.

# **Work Experience**

CEWE, Leamington Spa – UX Designer

#### January 2019 - Present

- · Improved usability of website through usability testing and depth interviews
- Increased Conversion Rate using A/B tests and heat maps
- United team around UX goals by delivering workshops and presentations
- Supplied user flows and wireframes to dev team for implementation

CEWE, Leamington Spa, UK — Web Designer

#### January 2018 - December 2018

- · Developed a modular design system using HTML and CSS
- · Supported marketing team with web assets and print work
- Directed product photo shoots to clearly communicate product features

Freelance Designer, Melbourne AU

#### March 2017 - December 2017

- $\bullet$  Designed and built emails for the EDM team at The Just Group
- Designed website using Odoo as an ecommerce platform for Korb
- Produced three product brochures as well as other assets for Korb
- Designed ways to communicate vast amounts of data for Korb

Attitude Design, Nottingham, UK – Junior Designer

## March 2016 - Oct 2016

- · Delivered brand identity, marketing and web design artwork
- · Worked on all stages of projects for conception to finishing artwork
- · Participated in brainstorming sessions and workshops with clients

## Tools

Adobe Photoshop\* Adobe Analytics Sketch\*
Adobe InDesign\* Adobe Target InVision
Adobe Illustrator ScreenFlow Hotjar
Adobe XD Camtasia Atom

# Education

Professional Diploma - UX Design

July 2018 - January 2019

UX Design Institute /

Glasgow Caledonian University

Bachelor of Music – Music Performance

October 2009 - July 2012

University of West London

Higher Diploma – Music Performance

October 2008 - July 2009

University of West London

BTEC National Diploma – Fine Art

September 2006 - 2008 July

Solihull Sixth Form College

# Skills

Research:

**Usability Testing** 

Depth Interviews

Online Surveys

Analytics

Competitive Benchmarking

Design:

Interaction Design

Wireframing

Prototyping

User Flows

Information Architecture

Coding:

HTML5 (intemtediate) CSS3 (intermediate) JavaScript (basic) PHP (basic)